http://www.edgertonhospital.com/privacy/

Web Privacy Policies and Procedures
Edgerton Hospital and Health Services (EHHS) respects your privacy. This document outlines the ways that EHHS web site may collect information from you. Browsing the Site Generally speaking, you can visit the pages of the EHHS web site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information. To learn more about who visits our site, we may track Internet domain addresses (that is, where you are connecting to the web site from, for instance from aol.com). While we log this address information, you will remain anonymous. We do not access or record such information as your log-in name at aol.com, and we use the information that is recorded for statistical purposes only. There are portions of the EHHS web sites that may request personal information:
Web Form Pages
Other portions of the site require personal information in order for you to complete such activities as purchasing community education classes, Foundation donations, subscribing to discussion lists or forums, or contacting EHHS staff members. These pages will ask you to enter such personal information as your name, social security number (for on-line employment applications), mailing address, phone numbers, e-mail address, and credit card information (for future e-commerce applications). The information that you type in these forms is necessary to complete the action which the page is used for. You may choose whether to enter this personal information. You are not required to do so. However, if you choose not to provide the information that we request, you may be unable to complete an action online and/or you may be unable to view portions of the web site.
Links to Other Sites
The EHHS web site includes links to other web sites. EHHS is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those sites. You should always read the privacy policy at a web site before revealing any personal information.
Links Policy
What We Link
EHHS publishes electronic links to certain web sites ONLY if they fit the needs of our customers and employees. EHHS’s web site link policy guidelines include, but are not limited to, the following:
1. External links are a good source of noncommercial information relevant to EHHS patients and visitors.
2. External links must be relevant to EHHS's mission and values.
3. If a web site or the web site's sponsor is engaged in unlawful activities or in activities that are incongruent with our mission and values, EHHS will NOT permit links to such a web site.
4. EHHS reserves the right to reject or remove links to any web site if we find the site content inappropriate. Links to web sites outside EHHS web sites are provided for convenience and information only, and we assume no responsibility for their content. Please read the Terms of Use statement for further details and liability disclaimer.
Quick Links
My Chart
Events & Classes
Find a Provider
Pay My Bill
Make a Gift
About Us
CEO's Message Awards and Recognition Administration Board of Trustees Our History Community Health Needs Assessment FoundationNondiscrimination Statement
Patients & Visitors
Medical Billing InfoPrivacy, Quality and Safety Patient & Family Services Online Bill PayDining Services Apply for Charity Care
Health & Wellness
Community Education Classes Healthy Village & Gardens Health/Community Links Speakers Available Community Connection NewsletterSilver Sneakers Site
Contact Us
Phone: 608.884.3441 Toll Free: 800.884.3441 11101 North Sherman Rd. Edgerton, WI 53534 Email
